http://www.elgin.edu/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Classes are in session. Access to campus remains limited to ensure everyone's safety. Face coverings are required. Student Services are available by appointment. See Campus Central for details.
Classes are in session. Access to campus remains limited to ensure everyone's safety. Face coverings are required. Student Services are available by appointment. See Campus Central for details.
Classes are in session. Access to campus remains limited to ensure everyone's safety. Face coverings are required. Student Services are available by appointment. See Campus Central for details.
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Texto en español.
Personally Identifiable Information
ECC will not collect personally identifiable information about you (name, address, social security number, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it voluntarily. If you do submit personal data we may use it in the following ways: to complete a request or order; to assist us in better understanding the needs of our constituents to improve our products and services; to reply to or contact you. ECC will not sell, rent or market personal data to third parties.
Please note that ECC may contact you via non-secure email. Please do not include information in an email that you would not want someone else to know.
Children 13 years old and younger
Individuals under the age of 13 must get parental consent to send personal information through the ECC Web site or via email. For more information on the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 please visit the Federal Trade Commission Web site http://www.ftc.gov/ogc/coppa1.htm.
All information collected for children 13 years of age or younger, including all contact information, is used solely for the purpose of ECC. ECC may use the contact information to confirm registration, provide current and future course information, provide information on upcoming course offerings and college events, confirm payment, and mailings related to ECC.
Non-personally identifiable information collected automatically and cookies
In some cases, information that is not personally identifiable may be automatically collected and/or logged. For example, information about the browser, operating system, IP address, and the domain name of sites that are linked to the ECC Web site. When you view the ECC Web site, some information may be stored on your computer. These “cookies” allow us to tailor a Web site or advertisement to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet browsers, you can alter user preferences to erase cookies from your hard drive, block cookies, or have it prompt you to either accept or refuse to store the cookie. Refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.
Third-party Web sites
ECC Web sites may provide links to Internet Web sites that are maintained by third parties. If you use these links, you will leave the ECC site and are subject to the privacy policy of that new site. ECC is not responsible for and does not endorse or evaluate the content or usefulness of information obtained from other sites. If you decide to access a third-party site linked to an ECC Web site, you do so at your own risk.
Disclaimer for Users and Third-party sites
ECC is not responsible for or liable for any defamatory, negligent, inaccurate, offensive or illegal conduct by users of this website or third-party sites. If ECC has to take legal action against any user of this website for inappropriate use, content or any violation of the above, user agrees to hold harmless and indemnify ECC for all costs and fees, including reasonable attorneys’ fees.
Rave Alert Emergency Notification System
ECC partners with Rave Mobile Safety to offer an emergency notification system called 'Rave Alert' to deliver reliable emergency text and email messages to employees and students any time there is an emergency or safety issue for the campus community. You are automatically signed up if you are an administrator, staff, current and/or prospective student.
ECC respects your right to privacy and honors requests to be removed from the Rave system. To opt-out please visit the Rave Alert Emergency Notification System web page.
Google Analytics
ECC uses Google Analytics, a web analytics tool that helps us understand how visitors engage with our website. Google Analytics uses cookies. The information available to us using Google Analytics is not personally identifiable. Visitors may opt-out of Google Analytics without affecting the user experience on elgin.edu.
ECC uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, which gives us access to information that we can use to approximate our website visitors' demographics and interests. This information will be used to improve the usability of the site and deliver more relevant content. Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting uses cookies. The information available to us using Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting is not personally identifiable. You can manage your settings for these cookies and opt-out of this feature by visiting Google Ads Settings.
ECC uses Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may display our ads on sites across the Internet. ECC and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on visitors past visits to our website.
*Please note: Opting out of Google Analytics will not does not affect the use of cookies being used on the elgin.edu website as indicated in the section titled ‘Non-personally identifiable information collected automatically and cookies'.
Campus Map with Google Maps API
ECC displays a map of the college that shows building information and the services we offer. ECC utilizes Google Maps API to:
Show campus information
Generate application functions (i.e., street view, satellite imagery, etc.)
Display personal information (i.e., driving directions from the address you specify)
Google will collect personal information, including the location of an individual. By using the campus map you are agreeing to be bound by Google's terms of use and privacy policy.
College Procedures
All administrative procedures
Registration procedures
Payment procedures
Financial aid policies
Student records procedures
Contact Us
Jobs at ECC
Elgin Community College. All Rights Reserved.
1700 Spartan Drive, Elgin, IL 60123 | 847-697-1000
